Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- State senate
  - Legislative
    - Bills introduced by ACB
      - SB 355 - Public social services (publicly soliciting) (Box 506)
        Copy of bill, brief description of bill
      - SB 356 - Public social services (Box 506)
      - SB 425 - State Highways (B.H. Freeway). f.1 of 2 (Box 506)
      - SB 217 - Meat labeling (grade). f.1 of 2 (Box 506)
        Copy of bill, memos, correspondence, booklet against bill, background information
      - SB 415 - Summons (Box 506)
        Copy of bill, correspondence. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - SB 415, undated. [3]l. Typescript.
      - SB 425 - State Highways (B.H. Freeway). f.2 of 2 (Box 506)
      - SB 433 - Contraceptives for minors. f.1 of 2 (Box 506)
      - SB 433 - Contraceptives for minors. f.2 of 2 (Box 506)
      - SB 527 - Abortion (hospitals) (Box 506)
        Copy and analysis of bill, correspondence, brief description of bill
      - SB 528 - Perishable foods: pull date (Box 506)
        Copy of bill, background information. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 528, 1972 Jun 14. 4l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 567 - Prophylactics (Box 507)
        Copy and analysis of bill, correspondence, background information. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 567, 1972 May 11. 6l. Typescript (photocopy)
      - SB 624 - Hospital licensing (Box 507)
      - SB 663 - Cable television (Box 507)
      - SB 620 - Undergrounding (Box 507)
        Copy of bill, untitled draft describing bill, correspondence
      - SB 618 - Consumer credit reporting act (Box 507)
      - SB 586 - Deeds of trust (Box 507)
      - SB 565 - Trading stamps (Box 507)
        Copy and analysis of bill, background information, brief description. Also: Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 565, 1972 Apr 20. 4l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 662 - Air pollution (Box 507)
      - SB 661 - Air pollution (Box 507)
        Copy and analysis of bill, final report - mandatory vehicle emission inspection and maintenance
      - SB 659 - Air pollution (Box 507)
      - SB 658 - Air pollution (Box 507)
      - SB 622 - Hospital licensing act (Box 507)
      - SB 657 - Air pollution (Box 507)
        Copy and analysis of bill, memos, correspondence, background information. Includes: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson relating to SB 657, undated. [2]l. Typescript (printer copy) with holograph corrections. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson on motor vehicle air pollution legislation: SB 657, 659, 661, undated. 8l. Typescript (photocopy)
      - SB 664 - Margarine (Box 507)
        Copy and analysis of bill, correspondence. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 664, 1972 Apr 25. [5]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 707 - Billboards. f.2 of 2 (Box 507)
      - SB 660 - Air pollution (Box 507)
      - SB 619 - Business trans. with women (Box 507)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, articles
      - SB 707 - Billboards. f.1 of 2 (Box 507)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, background information. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 707, 1972 Jun 22.5l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1338 - Off - road motorcycles (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill, brief description of bill. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 1338, 1972 Jun 26. 2l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1284 - Drug product selection (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, background information. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson, 1972 Nov 15. [2]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1287 - Administrative regs (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, untitled draft of bill's purpose, correspondence
      - SB 1332 - Conflict of interest (Box 508)
      - SB 1333 - Conflict of interest (Box 508)
      - SB 1334 - Vehicle inspection (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, correspondence. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 1334, 1972 Jun 12. [5]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1337 - Community property (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, memos, background information. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson -SB 1337 community property, 1972 Jun 16. [4]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1283 - Practice of medicine (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, brief description of bill, background information
      - SB 1286 - Prescriptions (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, brief description of bill. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson regarding SB 1286, undated. 3l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1335 - Mortgages and deeds of trust (Box 508)
      - SB 708 - Billboard tax (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, brief description of bill. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 708, 1972 Jun 22. [3]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 802 - Human whole blood production (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill, memo, articles. Also: AB 285 statement, undated. 4l. Typescript (photocopy)
      - SB 994 - Labeling of food containers (Box 508)
      - SB 996 - Mosquito abatement districts (Box 508)
      - SB 997 - Therapeutic abortion reporting (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill, brief description
      - SB 999 - Medi - Cal (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, brief description
      - SB 1331 - Conflict of interest (Box 508)
      - SB 801 - Food sanitation violations. f.1 of 2 (Box 508)
      - SB 1254 - Conflict of interest (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, brief description of bill, letter
      - SB 800 - Sec. obligations (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, correspondence, brief description of bill
      - SB 799 - Used car sales (Box 508)
      - SB 801 - Food sanitation violation. f.2 of 2 (Box 508)
      - SB 709 - Public social services (welfare report. recommendations) (Box 508)
      - SB 1000 - Communicable disease prevention (Box 508)
      - SB 1001 - New community development (Box 508)
      - SB 1003 - Elections (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson on SB 1003, 1972 Jun 8. 3l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1004 - Elections (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill, brief background information
      - SB 1005 - Electrical facilities (Box 508)
      - SB 1006 - Fish and game (Box 508)
      - SB 1247 - Noise control act of 1972 (Box 508)
        Copy of bill. Also: Draft: Statement on SB 1247 (office of noise control), undated. [2]l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1248 - Noise standards (mach. and equip) (Box 508)
        Copy and analysis of bill, memos
      - SB 1250 - Airport noise standards (Box 508)
      - SB 1251 - Drunk driving (Box 508)
      - SB 1252 - Victims of crime (Box 508)
      - SB 1253 - Conflict of interest (Box 508)
      - SB 710 - PUC rate increases (Box 508)
        Copy of bill, background information, brief description of bill. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson regarding Senate Bill 710, 1972 Apr 27. 3l. Typescript (printer copy)
      - SB 1364 - Taxation (Box 509)
      - SB 1363 - Experimental ambulatory health delivery system (Box 509)
      - SB 1359 - Food adulteration (Box 509)
      - SB 1357 - Alcoholic beverages: beer (Box 509)
      - Abortion statistics (Box 509)
      - SB 1339 - Real property loans (Box 509)
        Copy of bill, background information, correspondence, brief description of bill, articles. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson - Senate Bill No. 1339, 1972 Jun 15. [3]l. Typescript (print copy) with holograph corrections
      - SB 1366 - Parks (development) (Box 509)
    - Research
      - Coastal legislation (Box 475, Folder 4)
      - The scenic route: A guide for the designation of an official scenic highway (Box 475, Folder 6)
      - Vehicle noise (Box 475, Folder 11)
      - Proposed legislation smog (Box 475, Folder 12)
      - Environment. f.1 of 2 (Box 475, Folder 13)
      - Environment. f.2 of 2 (Box 475, Folder 14)
      - Environmental legislation (Box 475, Folder 15)
      - Pesticides (Box 475, Folder 16)
      - Environment (Box 476, Folder 1)
      - Family planning (Box 476, Folder 2)
      - Air pollution. f.1 of 1 (Box 476, Folder 3)
      - Air pollution. f.2 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 4)
      - Medical and psychological effects. f.1 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 5)
      - Medical and psychological effects. f.2 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 6)
      - Air pollution. f.1 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 7)
      - Air pollution. f.2 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 8)
      - Gasoline (Box 476, Folder 9)
      - Air pollution (Box 476, Folder 10)
      - Funeral (Box 476, Folder 11)
      - Funeral reform (Box 476, Folder 12)
        Correspondence, general materials
      - Funeral reform. f.1 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 13)
      - Funeral reform. f.2 of 2 (Box 476, Folder 14)
      - A.B. 1871 - Funeral practices. f.1 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 1)
      - A.B. 1871 - Funeral practices. f.2 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 2)
      - Funeral bill (Box 477, Folder 3)
      - Funeral reform. f.1 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 4)
      - Funeral reform. f.2 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 5)
      - Funeral reform (Box 477, Folder 6)
      - Funerals. f.1 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 7)
      - Funerals. f.2 of 2 (Box 477, Folder 8)
      - Death (definition) (Box 477, Folder 9)
      - Funeral directors and embalmers law (Box 477, Folder 10)
      - Law in transition quarterly (Box 477, Folder 11)
      - Pageant (Box 477, Folder 12)
      - Funeral bill - letters (Box 478, Folder 1)
      - Reports (air pollution). f.1 of 2 (Box 478, Folder 2)
      - Reports (air pollution). f.2 of 2 (Box 478, Folder 3)
      - Auto repair (Box 478, Folder 4)
      - Original articles (Box 478, Folder 5)
      - Mechanic's certification (Box 478, Folder 6)
      - Implementation of SB 51. f.1 of 2 (Box 479, Folder 1)
        Correspondence, press release, articles
      - Implementation of SB 51. f.2 of 2. (Box 479, Folder 2)
      - Auto mechanics (Box 479, Folder 3)
      - Mechanics certification. f.1 of 2 (Box 479, Folder 4)
      - Mechanics certification. f.2 of 2 (Box 479, Folder 5)
      - Mechanic licensing (Box 479, Folder 6)
      - Mechanic licensing article (Box 480, Folder 1)
      - The case for mechanic's certification (Box 480, Folder 2)
      - Nurse - midwives (Box 480, Folder 3)
      - Mechanic's certification (Box 480, Folder 4)
      - Automotive repair. f.1 of 2 (Box 480, Folder 5)
      - Automotive repair. f.2 of 2 (Box 480, Folder 6)
      - Licensing of automotive repair dealers (Box 480, Folder 7)
      - SB 462 - Press on California Therapeutic Abortion Act (Box 483)
      - SB 462 - Press on California Therapeutic Abortion Act (Box 483)
      - SB 462 - Witness statements (support) (Box 483)
      - Abortion - ACB statement (Box 484)
        Articles. Also: Statement by Senator Anthony C. Beilenson on Therapeutic Abortion Act, 1967 Apr 27. 7l. Typescript (photocopy)
      - Abortion - general press (Box 484)
      - Abortion - press. f.2 of 2 (Box 484)
      - SB 462 - support letters (Box 484)
      - Abortion - congratulations (Box 484)
        Letters
      - Abortion Lists (Box 484)
      - SB 51 - Auto repair. f.1 of 2 (Box 484)
        Copy of bill, correspondence. Untitled press release to crack down on auto repair fraud. 1971 Nov 22. [2]l. Also: Statement of Senator Anthony C. Beilenson re Senate bill 51, 1971 May 13. 4l. Printer copy with holograph corrections
      - SB 51 - Auto repair. f.2 of 2 (Box 484)
      - SB 497 - Sexual crimes (Box 484)
      - SB 523 - Service of process (Box 484)
        Correspondence, report on enrolled bill
      - SB 546 - Population study (Box 484)
        Analysis of senate bill, report on enrolled bill
      - Abortion - press. f.1 of 2 (Box 484)
  - Press releases
    - Originals (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - Top bills (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - Unit Pricing (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Teenage illegitimate birth rates (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - Meat labeling (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - New car dealers board (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - Open dating of dairy products (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - Mechanic certification (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - Blast at Reagan on welfare caseload decrease (Box 474, Folder 9)
    - Beverly Hills freeway (Box 474, Folder 10)
    - Birth control info to minors (Box 474, Folder 11)
    - Trading stamps (Box 474, Folder 12)
    - Billboards (Box 474, Folder 13)
    - PUC rate increases (Box 474, Folder 14)
    - Noise pollution (Box 474, Folder 15)
    - $25 tax break (Box 474, Folder 16)
    - Bureaucratic lawlessness (Box 474, Folder 17)
    - Laurel child care center (Box 474, Folder 18)
    - H and W hearing on Sep 8 (Box 474, Folder 19)
    - Funeral reform (Box 474, Folder 20)
    - Hereditary diseases (Box 474, Folder 21)
    - Telephone company (Box 474, Folder 22)
    - D.O. scholarships (Box 474, Folder 23)
    - Yes on Proposition 20 (Box 474, Folder 24)
    - No on Proposition 21 (Box 474, Folder 25)
    - College grants (Box 474, Folder 26)
    - Veto of SB 433 (Box 474, Folder 27)
    - Pregnancy test kits (Box 474, Folder 28)
    - SB 1249 signed (Box 474, Folder 29)
  - Research
    - Outline of major provisions in our no -fault bill (SB 354) (Box 474, Folder 36)
    - Comparison of no - fault bills (Box 474, Folder 38)
      SB 40, AB 125, SB 384, SB 354
    - List of 1972 consumer bills (Box 474, Folder 39)
    - List of 1972 population control bill (Box 474, Folder 40)
  - Statements by ACB
    - Trading stamps - SB 565 (Box 474, Folder 31)
    - Prophylactics - SB 567 (Box 474, Folder 32)
    - Dairy product pull date - SB 234 (Box 474, Folder 33)
    - Margarine - SB 664 (Box 474, Folder 34)
    - No - fault auto insurance - SB 354 (Box 474, Folder 35)
    - Cable television - SB 663 (Box 474, Folder 37)
    - Cremated remains - SB 730 (Box 474, Folder 41)
    - Sterilization operations - SB 1358 (Box 474, Folder 42)
    - Motor vehicle emission control - SB 659 (Box 474, Folder 43)
  - Statements by ACB releases
    - Mechanic certification - SB 292 (Box 474, Folder 30)
- U.S. Senate
  - Campaign
    - Announcement
      - For the year dated (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Clippings
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Clippings [another folder]
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - General
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Good clippings
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 4)
        So labeled
    - History
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Press releases
      - For the year dated (Box 205, Folder 6)